KEVIN BOST FRONT END WEB ENGINEERING

864-420-2756 - kevbost@gmail.com - 121-B Line Street, Charleston, SC - 29403

PROFILE

I am a young programmer saturated with enthusiasm for finding my place in the programmers' work force. Successful problem solving drives my work and makes the challenge of coding enjoyable and exciting. I am ready to work hard and closely with my colleagues to create a modern web experience. Putting languages in to easily understandable terms for people with and without technical knowledge is one of my favorite things.

TOOLBOX

Languages: Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, SASS, AJAX, GIT, Javascript, jQuery, BackboneJS, Parses,

UnderscoreJS, PaperJS, MomentJS, Twitter Bootstrap, Grunt, Yeoman, Bower, NPM

Design: Proficient in Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Lightroom

Office: Experience use of Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, Google Docs Suite, Enspire

OS: Advanced use of OSX, Microsoft Windows 7 and XP

EXPERIENCE

MITCHELL INDUSTRIAL CONTROLS — 2012-2014

Industrial Heating Solutions – I wore many hats at MICC, raw data entry, invoicing, mechanical drawing and physical measurement, order processing, purchasing, customer relations, product photography, industrial controller custom programming, inventory management, and shipping & receiving.

I was given the opportunity to learn professional lessons in a field I had no previous experience in and interact with technology and materials not available or useful to the general public. This experience helped me to gain knowledge on the ins and outs of a professional environment.

GREENVILLE ORGANIC FOODS ORGANIZATION (GOFO) — 2010-2014

Community Education, Non Profit - "Tech guy", web maintenance / re-design / consultant, Promotional print media design, file system restructuring and relocation, photographer.

I came to GOFO looking for community service hours for college, and enjoyed it so much I stayed for 4 years. The office is located next to CoWork (a collection of the best web/software engineers and designers in Greenville, SC), where I often imagined myself working.

EDUCATION

THE IRON YARD - 2014

The Iron Yard's Front End Web Design and Engineering program is a web development accelerator that prepares its students to enter the professional world as knowledgeable and confident programmers.

VIRGINIA INTERMONT COLLEGE - 2007-2010

Photography and Digital Imaging - Photographic theory and implementation, advanced darkroom knowledge, advanced Photoshop, advanced digital printing, photographic history, modern photographic theory.